<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>osinimu - blog</title><link href="https://osinimu.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://osinimu.github.io/feeds/blog.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://osinimu.github.io/</id><updated>2017-07-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated><subtitle> Data scientist, Writer &amp; Outlier </subtitle><entry><title>The profitable Neighbourhoods in lagos for investing in property.</title><link href="https://osinimu.github.io/the-profitable-neighbourhoods-in-lagos-for-investing-in-property.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-07-21T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-07-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Osinimu</name></author><id>tag:osinimu.github.io,2017-07-21:/the-profitable-neighbourhoods-in-lagos-for-investing-in-property.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Best Neighbourhoods in Lagos for investing in property.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Are you thinking about buying a property in Lagos State, Nigeria and then renting it out? Then you should stick around to find out the best neighbourhoods to consider.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually, how do we go about deciding which Lagos neighbourhood is the least or most profitable? Home to over 14 million people, Lagos is on its way to becoming the &lt;a href="http://www.citymayors.com/statistics/urban_2020_1.html"&gt;seventh largest urban area in the world by 2020&lt;/a&gt;. This is right after recently obtaining the mega city status. In a society where owning property is regarded as a massive achievement, until you own a property you’re not viewed as one who has accomplished much. Real estate is quite the big deal around these parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Property prices in the nation’s former capital are constantly on the rise along with property owners incessantly increasing rent prices. With the massive expansion ongoing in Lagos, property in the suburbs could soon be at home in commercial neighbourhoods instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s an outcry over a housing problem in Lagos but the bane of this problem isn’t that there are no houses. Actually there are empty houses all over the city; with some staying vacant over a year without being rented out. This is quite the headache for someone looking to invest in Lagos real estate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some housing projects remain unoccupied because they are pricey in some neighbourhoods notably Lekki, VI, Ikoyi and Yaba. Nonetheless, developers/investors continue to put up more housing projects. To help navigate through the property market in Lagos, let’s identify which neighbourhoods offer more property investment value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal neighbourhood for investing in properties would have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High rental price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low sale price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Web Scraping tolet.com.ng&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to collect house pricing data in Lagos for both rental and for sale properties after looking at three major websites; &lt;a href="https://www.property24.com/"&gt;Property24&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.privateproperty.com.ng/"&gt;Privateproperty&lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.tolet.com.ng/"&gt;Tolet&lt;/a&gt;. Compared to the other websites, Tolet search results reveal more information, with the format of each listing being consistent which is splendid for web scraping. (This analysis is based on active listings on tolet.com.ng as at 23/08/2017).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I web scraped tolet.com.ng using the python scrapy library, then created two spiders, one each for rent and sale properties. I then made a list of 40 Lagos neighbourhoods and categorised each listing address into one of these neighbourhoods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certain neighbourhoods were categorised into one e.g Magodo Phases 1 and 2, Shangisha was categorised into Ikosi and also Lekki Phases 1 and 2 into Lekki.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="List of neighborrhoods in Lagos" src="/images/neigh.PNG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Cleaning and Manipulating the data&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the listings in both the sale and rent datasets, the price columns contained unwanted text like; “_/ year”, “ / sqm” , and “ / day”. _Such text was discarded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new column for categorising each listing’s address into a singular neighborhood was created. This was called “Neighborhood”. The neighborhood of each listing was obtained by matching the list of neighbourhoods created earlier against corresponding listing addresses, and outputting the first match as the values for the neighbourhood column.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Finding the Least/Most investable neighbourhoods in Lagos&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After cleaning up the data it was time for some analysis. Needing a way to evaluate each neighbourhood, I had to compare the rental and sale prices. So for each neighbourhood I calculated the average price for properties, up for rent and for sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="avg price for rent and sale" src="/images/avg_prices.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;calculate average price for both rental and sale properties&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s have a look at the dataset before we start weighing the rental and sale prices. I observed from the data set that some neighbourhoods have very few listings or almost none at all. Epe and Ijora both had just 1 listing each, while Ifako-Ijaiye had 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="dataset lookup" src="/images/sas.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Average prices for sale and rent properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The low number of listings can introduce imbalance and also lead to incorrect results. Hence I excluded neighbourhoods with less than or equal to five listings to guarantee the quality of the data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Visualizing the number of listings" src="/images/download.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualizing the number of listings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some Instances of neighbourhoods with more than 5 listings are; Ajah with an average sale and rent price of 108,854,718.358 Naira and 1,041,328.82 Naira respectively, Apapa with an average sale and rent price of 26303458333.333 Naira and 16702858.065 Naira respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Neighbourhoods with more than 5 listings" src="/images/husey.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neighbourhoods with more than 5 listings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can look for a linear relationship between the average sale price and the average rent price; if it costs more to buy, it should cost more to rent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would also be considering the outliers in this linear regression. Outliers are data points that do not follow the general trend of the rest of the data. There are two types of outliers in our plot below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outliers that are located above the regression line with abnormally high sale price (Orile, Apapa)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outliers that are located below the regression line with abnormally low sale price (Ikoyi)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Type 2 outliers are more likely to be profitable and Type 1 outliers are less likely to be profitable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Linear regression plot of rent prices ~ sale prices" src="/images/reg-code.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linear regression plot of rent prices ~ sale prices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Linear regression plot of rent prices ~ sale prices" src="/images/linear-regression.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualization of the linear relationship between average rent and sale price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Examining the plot above, we can see points above and below the regression line. Outliers are the extreme cases in these circumstances. The points above the regression line have a higher average sale value than the fitted values, signifying that they are less likely to be profitable. On the other hand, the point below the regression line has a higher average rental price than the fitted values hinting at the tendency of being profitable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compared to other apartments with over ₦10,000,000 average rental price, Ikoyi has the lowest average sale price of ₦867,429,147,alluding to its profitability given rental price is over ₦10,000,000. However it is not clarified that Ikoyi is the most profitable neighbourhood when compared to the other neighbourhoods below the regression line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance Ejigbo with an average sale price of ₦32,647,058.824 and an average rent price of ₦1,325,000 is far more profitable than Ikoyi with an average sale price of ₦867,429,147 and an average rent price of ₦11,131,547 Naira. Even though Ejigbo is not an outlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To precisely ascertain the profitabilities, I computed the ratio of average rent price over average sale price and plotted the distribution of the ratios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Distribution of the ratio of average rent price to average sale price
" src="/images/ratio-dist.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distribution of the ratio of average rent price to average sale price&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this analysis, the top 5 least profitable neighbourhoods are listed, with the results matching the linear regression analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Top 5 leat Profitable Neighbourhoods in Lagos
" src="/images/least-profitable.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top 5 least Profitable Neighbourhoods in Lagos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top 5 most profitable neighbourhoods are shown beneath, with Ikorodu and Ejigbo leading the way. We can see here that Ikoyi isn’t even in the top 5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Top 5  Profitable Neighbourhoods in Lagos
" src="/images/top-profitable.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top 5 Profitable Neighbourhoods in Lagos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The properties in these neighbourhoods have a low sale price and a high rental price. So if you’re contemplating investing in some real estate, buying properties from these neighbourhoods and putting them up for rent would be worth your while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Challenges&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it would be nice to claim this entire exercise was a breeze, it would be dishonest to leave out the challenges I faced. As with any meaningful endeavour in life, there were a few mitigating factors to deal with. The bigger issues included:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigating round the poorly planned city addresses. Street names have ambiguous formats like; “Awolowo Way,” “Obafemi Awolowo Way” or “Chief Obafemi Awolowo Way,” and it’s confusing to know which exactly is which. This issue led me to group the the listings into the most common/general neighbourhoods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I intended to compare the rent and sale properties by getting their price averages and dividing that by their sizes(per square meters). Tragically, a dearth of information on the sizes of listed houses, on the websites referenced earlier forced my hand . I had to settle for just the average prices as the benchmark for comparing the rent and sale properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This analysis doesn’t account for taxes, mortgage, insurance payments, and other fees. It can be improved upon by going ahead to predict house prices using machine learning, if a more detailed dataset is made available. The dataset for future exploration would include characteristics such as; size per square meter of a property, unemployment rate, school rating, distance to major employment centres, accessibility to highways, and etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I found such data difficult to access.The availability of such statistics in public domain would provide much more insight into how these factors all affect property prices..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This information could be very useful for future investments and research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The full code for this analysis can be found here: &lt;a href="https://github.com/osisieke/tolet-housing-price-analysis/"&gt;https://github.com/osisieke/tolet-housing-price-analysis/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>What customers on Twitter think about Nigerian ecommerce companies</title><link href="https://osinimu.github.io/what-customers-on-twitter-think-about-nigerian-ecommerce-companies.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-04-03T10:20:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-04-03T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Osinimu</name></author><id>tag:osinimu.github.io,2017-04-03:/what-customers-on-twitter-think-about-nigerian-ecommerce-companies.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's twitter users and their thoughs on the countrys ecommerce companies.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In a country bereft with inadequate data and in some instances, an alarming absence of data, while the biggest purveyors of the limited collated data, hoard it. Any form of data collation in Nigeria is seen as gold. The range of information conveyed through social media, is limitless. Often these short messages are used to share opinions and sentiments that people have about what is going on in the world around them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter constitutes a rich source of data that can be used for obtaining information about any topic imaginable. This data can be used in different use cases such as finding trends related to a specific keyword, measuring brand sentiment, and gathering feedback about new products and services. This post was inspired by &lt;a href="https://theartandscienceofdata.wordpress.com/2016/10/09/what-twitter-feels-about-network-providers-in-nigeria/#more-442"&gt;Rosebud Anwuri's post&lt;/a&gt; on Nigerian telcos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to extract data from Twitter about Nigerian e-commerce companies and analyze what customers perceive of these brands, which can in turn help us find out how good their services are. This process is called sentiment analysis. Sentiment analysis is a type of text analytics, a process of determining the emotional tone behind a set of words, gaining an understanding of the the attitudes, opinions and emotions expressed within an online mention. Using this approach I analyzed sentiments in tweets by providing a positive or negative score based on words and Emojis (emoticons). Words like 'angry', 'vex', 'annoyed' appearing in a tweet tend to produce a negative sentiment score while words like 'love', 'like', 'amazed' would do the opposite.Unlike documents, working with informal text genres (like tweets) presents challenges for Natural language processing beyond those typically encountered when working with more traditional text genres. Tweets are short: a sentence or a headline rather than a document. The language used in tweets is very informal, with creative spelling and punctuation, misspellings, slang, new words, URLs, and genre-specific terminology and abbreviations, such as, RT for "retweet" and #hashtags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_ Note: it is important point out that Twitter is a very small sample of any e-commerce company's customer base. This means that what may be true for this sample might not necessarily apply to the general population._&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I collected tweets about four nigerian e-commerce companies (konga, jumia, payporte and yudala) from the 28th June to the 6th of July using the &lt;strong&gt;Twittr&lt;/strong&gt; package in R. The collected twitter data came with attributes such as: The tweet, the day and time it was posted, the username who posted and the amount of retweets/favorite the tweet posted. Next thing i did was to clean the tweets removing punctuations, trailing and leading spaces, URLs and other things that don't help the analysis, using the Stringr package. Unsurprisingly the bulk of the time spent was on data cleaning. While the cleaning process was on,i came across a discovery about People talking about konga but were referring to the nigerian musician while others talked about a game named donkey konga. After the tweets were cleaned up, I extracted the emoticons from the tweets and put their descriptions in the tweet data file, having noted that emoticons affords us lots of information. Using the &lt;a href="https://finnaarupnielsen.wordpress.com/2011/03/16/afinn-a-new-word-list-for-sentiment-analysis/"&gt;AFINN&lt;/a&gt; lexicon which gives a sentiment score between -5 to 5 for several words i scored the sentiment of each tweet. I created wordclouds using the &lt;strong&gt;wordcloud&lt;/strong&gt; package after converting the tweets to a clean corpus using the &lt;strong&gt;tm&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;SnowballC&lt;/strong&gt; package. The code can be found &lt;a href="https://github.com/osisieke/Twitter-sentiment-analysis"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The visualizations of the final data was done using &lt;strong&gt;Tableau&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets see some interesting things about each individual ecommerce company that we found. If you want to have a closer look at the visualizations I'll be using, that can be found &lt;a href="https://public.tableau.com/profile/christopher.ajulo#!/vizhome/Book1_21337/Dashboard1"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jumia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the frontrunners of in the Nigerian e-commerce scene, jumia operates a model based on both business-to-consumer e-commerce and an online marketplace, which allows retailers to sell their products to customers online via Jumia's platform. With over 14 hubs and its own delivery fleet, jumia has a target population reach exceeding 75%. How much are they utilizing their resources to their advantage and their customer's? Let's have a look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With an average sentiment score of 0.8, jumia isn't doing bad at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first chart is a trend chart with the yellow line showing the number of tweets and the blue line the average sentiment score. The chart shows that the higher the tweets about jumia the higher the sentiment score. This means that most of the people tweet about jumia when they feel good about them. The second chart shows the emojis related to jumia and their frequency. 71% of the emojis used are positive emojis which reinforces that customers on twitter like jumia. The third chart shows when customers tweet the most about jumia. The peakest hour for customers tweets is by 7am. Customers tweet the most in the mornings and it dwindles as the day goes by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The size of the words in the wordcloud shows how frequently they were used. The words are mostly positive words with words like joy, smile, discount, just, face and hope being displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Konga&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently konga revealed they have 184,000 active customers (approximately 1.1% of the Nigerian population) kind of disappointing right?I know. Seeing as they are arguably nigeria's biggest internet platform. Are they living up to the hype?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The average sentiment score for konga is 0.76, just below jumia's. I was'nt surprised that that they have the sencond lowest score as they get a lot of stick online. The number of tweets about konga is more consistent than its other competitors. Of all the companies konga had the most negative emojis related to them from a crying face to danger. It's hard to say which time of the day most customers tweet about konga,only that the peakest time for tweets are mostly odd hours of the day. Generally konga gets the most interactions on twitter. Their customers are talking, they just have to listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at their wordcloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most used keywords are a mixture of positive and negative words. The words that are incomplete are due to the process called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stemming"&gt;stemming&lt;/a&gt;, that reduces certain words to their base or root form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payporte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official sponsor of the recently concluded Big Brother Nigeria reality show, payporte wasn't quite known till they were the lead sponsor for the show. The awareness garnered by payporte due to its marketing strategy whilst sponsoring big brother was massive and it's still paying massive dividends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payporte had the highest sentiment score with 1.1. Obviously the residue from the impact made by the reality show is still trickling down into their corner, while making strides to become the third biggest player in the nigerian e-commerce scene. The number of interactions (tweets) for payporte was very consistent with how their customers felt about them on certain day. 86% of the emojis used by customers where positive. Customers tweeted about payporte mostly at noon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here words like love, now, will, dancer, get and like can be seen. Not a lot of keywords stand out, eh?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yudala&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Launched in late 2015 as Nigeria's first e-commerce player that operates both an online platform and physical retail stores, giving it an edge over established online-only players such as Jumia and Konga. Even Though the omnichannel model seems to be untested by african retailers and is yet to yield dividends for yudala, there are a lot of safe bets on it. Giving voice to the notion that traditional model in Nigeria still has relevance. Lets see how yudala fares on twitter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yudala has an average sentiment score of 0.5. This is to be expected as they have the lesser of twitter interactions amongst its counterparts. The highest number of tweets they had on any particular day was 5 on the 31st of May. The emojis used in tweets were only two, both having a sentiment score of 0.Customers seem to tweet mostly at 1pm and their sentiment scores also peaks at that time. Customers of yudala seem to be indifferent to them online, could their strong offline presence be the reason?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's look at the most frequent words used in tweets about yudala.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of the words stand out as negative. Most of the words are generally positive ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customers of jumia are okay with their service, while&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;konga received most of the complaints of the four, the good words about them sort of overwhelmed those complaints, giving them a balance, still giving them a lot to think about&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A few customers related to jumia and konga's service to that of amazon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;payporte really milked out all they could from the Big brother show, hopefully they keep making such marketing strides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yudala being relatively new to the space have customers still undecided about them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took &lt;a href="http://www.wired.com/2015/10/get-used-to-amazon-being-a-profitable-company/"&gt;almost 20 years&lt;/a&gt; before Amazon delivered one dollar of profit from ecommerce but they now have a massive balance sheet and a lot of expertise learned from its mistakes. Since neither of the nigerian ecommerce companies are profitable yet, it would be easy to say the direction for at least one of the companies would be similar to amazon. Until you know that at most there are only 600k active customers shopping online in Nigeria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of changing customer behaviours is usually high, nonetheless that is the key if any of these companies will win in this space. The ability to quickly understand consumer attitudes and react accordingly is something that organizations should look to take advantage of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter is a relatively small sample of the customer base of any ecommerce company and the people that are mostly use twitter are millennials. Even Though this might be the target market, what may be true for this sample may not necessarily apply to the population/whole customer base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The time period for collecting these tweets is quite short ( 10 days). Maybe i'd keep collecting more tweets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's little possibility of a skew in the analysis due to a lot of promotional tweets (which i tried my best to filter out).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since Jumia isnt isnt only in nigeria,some tweets were from countries such as kenya and egypt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to say the analysis can be improved by using a deep learning algorithm, further analyze their delivery service and the quality of their products and also add other ecommerce platforms to the mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="./the-fine-art-of-relationships.html"&gt;The Fine art of relationships&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="./the-profitable-neighbourhoods-in-lagos-for-investing-in-property.html"&gt;The profitable Neighbourhoods in lagos for investing in property.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="./the-profitable-neighbourhoods-in-lagos-for-investing-in-property.html"&gt;The profitable Neighbourhoods in lagos for investing in property.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://christopherajulo.com"&gt;&lt;img alt="Avatar" src="theme/images/fosi.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://christopherajulo.com"&gt;Ajulo Christopher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you like this article? Share it with your friends!&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>